मैं तुम्हें कितने सालों से कह रहा हूँ
मुझे तुम्हें मेरा लंड चूसते हुए देखना पसंद है।
और मैं तुम्हें कितने सालों से बता रही हूँ?
रोशनी में मैं यह नहीं कर सकती।
सुबह के दो बज रहे हैं।
बस, अब बहुत हो गया, बेबी।
You know?
For years now, I mean,
for fucking years, every
everytime we do it, it's like the first time for you.
हर बार तुम्हारे लिए जैसे पहली बार होता है।
Patty.
Every time we fuck, it's like, it's like you're doing me a favor.
हर बार जब हम चुदाई करते हैं, ऐसा लगता है जैसे तुम मुझ पर एहसान कर रही हो।
ये तो कमाल है।
I mean, just because I don't like to do it with the light on.
मेरा मतलब है, सिर्फ इसलिए कि मुझे रोशनी में ऐसा करना पसंद नहीं है।
Is that any reason for you to leave?
क्या यह तुम्हारे जाने का कोई कारण है?
Yeah.
Where are you going?
It's your secretary.
It's Jean, isn't it?
Yep.
Well, you just don't tell your son.
No, no, wait, no, I'll tell him.
I'll tell him the shithill of a father is
leaving us for some teeny-bauper.
Well, listen, tell Paul upon tomorrow.
And if he wants to, he can live with me
and Jean.
I've had it with you.
I've had it.
You know, so long.
It's just something that's been coming on
for a long time.
You'll come back, ma'am.
You've had advice with Dad before?
Forget it.
He's not coming back.
He wants you to think about living with
him.
I'd rather stay with you.
Honey, it's a pretty big decision.
And I want you to think about it.
He's going to call you later.
I could quit school and get a job.
The hell with that?
You're not quitting school.
Now we'll make out.
I'll get a job.
I mean, I'm not exactly over the hill you
know.
And you tell me.
I got the best looking mom in town.
Why, thank you, sonny boy.
Oh, no.
Oh, Barbara.
Why are you doing up with this ungodly
hour?
Gina, you're not going to believe this.
I can hardly believe it myself.
Chris Watts out on me.
He didn't.
Son of a bitch left me for his teeny
brother's secretary.
Oh, you mean you're looking for a job?
Lunch?
Sure.
Yeah, that's fine.
Okay.
See it once, will you?
Wake up sleepyheads.
She wants some breakfast.
Mmm.
Hello darling.
Sit down.
You look terrible.
What you need isn't the ring.
Now, tell me what the hell got into Chris.
Can you imagine?
I still can't believe it myself.
I mean, that bastard leaving me and his
son for that bitch.
I bet she's a young.
Who's a little cunt?
I don't know.
I mean, who keeps track of secretaries?
1920?
I could have told you.
The minute they get it up, they let you
down.
Barbara, what you need is a new guy.
We'll find you a nice, sexy, young stud.
No thanks.
I think I need time for my ego to heal
first.
No sense in doing without your personal
shrink.
I insist, darling.
I know a real nice guy.
A little too old for me, but just perfect
for you.
How's the job hunting?
Are you kidding?
If you're over 25, they won't even look at
you.
I couldn't even get a job as a hooker.
Too bad.
That would have been exciting.
Wait a minute.
Who's that friend of yours and Chris's?
He got a divorce a few years ago,
and then he dropped out a side.
What's his name?
He always had eyes for you.
Jerry Morgan.
I didn't even think of him.
And his office is just a few blocks away.
At least it used to be.
I think I'll have fish today.
It'll remind me of Evelyn.
You remember when I lived with Evelyn?
Now, Barbara, tell me about that gorgeous
son of yours.
He must really be big by now.
Oh, well, you quit it.
Now, when was the Battle of Hastings?
You can open your legs.
You're losing my ears.
When was the Battle of Hastings?
1066.
Right.
Where are the Olympus Mountains?
Cyprus.
Wow.
When did Alexander conquer Cyprus?
333 BC.
Now, will you knock it off with a
question?
Oh, Paul.
We're so smart.
You got everyone right.
I think you deserve a reward.
Ooh, let's get that big, beautiful cock up
here to where we can see.
Oops.
Add it again.
I knew this would happen.
Are we studying history or sex education?
But Paul knows all the answers by heart.
We'll just copy his paper.
Boy, you never told me it was that big.
Well, I'll leave you two alone.
Hey, wait a minute.
Don't go.
Tell you what.
I'll let you lick it a little.
If you promise to give it back.
Promise, promise her.
What?
Okay, I promise.
And I don't have to give it right back.
Okay.
That's it.
Oh, wait, Paul.
I'm going first.
She's never calm.
Never calm.
Ever?
Come here.
I'm going to send you to the room.
Oh, fuck her heart.
Grab it.
Then move your hands so you can find all
the way.
That's so good.
Oh.
I'm sorry.
It's gonna feel good.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, it'll be one harder.
Oh.
Oh, I'm gonna do it.
I'm gonna do it.
Oh, I'm gonna come.
Paul, are you home?
Yeah, Mom.
Hey, I started dinner.
How's steak and salad sound?
Sounds great.
I'm famished.
God, am I tired.
Honey, did you speak to your father yet?
Yeah.
I'll talk to him.
Well?
Oh, Mom.
You know I'm gonna stay with you.
Oh, darling, I'm so glad.
You know, Mom, I've been thinking.
I'm gonna quit school and get a job.
I told you no way.
Your father's going to pay you schooling
expenses.
And besides, guess what?
What?
I got a job today.
You're kidding me.
Doin' what?
Where?
Well, remember Jerry Morgan?
He and his wife used to come over a few
years ago?
Yeah.
Well, I went to see him today.
His office is only a few blocks from here,
and he was kind enough to give me a job.
Even though I really don't think he needed
any extra help.
Well, that's great, working girl.
Come on, let's see.
Ah, yes, Mrs. Donovan.
I'm on my way out the door of this minute
to show you the property.
See you there.
Bye-bye.
Good night, Barbara.
Good night.
Hello?
I mean, Morgan Realty.
It's me.
Did Charlie call you?
Are you going out with him tonight?
Yes, he did.
And yes, I am.
Gina, are you sure this guy isn't going to
pull anything?
Charlie?
Charlie's a pussycat.
Excuse me, Barbara.
Just a second, Gina.
Hi, Jerry.
Barbara, could you stay for about five
minutes?
I have a very important letter.
I need to get out.
Sure, sure.
Gina, I gotta go.
I gotta type up a letter.
Gina, are you sure this guy won't try
anything?
Barbara, Charlie's afraid of girls.
You couldn't be safer in a church.
Okay, I'm just going out with him because
I trust you.
What?
Jerry, what are you doing?
What's going on over there?
Is Jerry raping you?
I don't shoot some of it, bitch!
No!
Stop it.
I don't want this and I don't need it.
Wait a minute, Barbara.
What's he doing?
Jerry, I would never have thought this of
you.
After all the years, we've known each
other, too.
Oh, Christ, Barbara.
I don't... I don't know if one came over.
I've always had this thing for you.
Even when...
I was married.
I'd look at her.
I'd look at you.
Promise me, you don't think you know?
But you're going to get a cut and pay
because you won't bother me.
Oh, my God.
That was exciting.
Oh, I thought he was raping her.
Oh, mother, you should have heard that.
Oh, I'm so turned on.
Oh, yeah.
Just play with my pussy.
You know how I like it, don't you?
Just bring your tongue down there.
Oh.
Don't stop.
Give your tongue there.
I know.
Let's take my panties off.
Mmm.
Isn't that better?
Oh, yeah.
Oh.
That's it.
Oh, yeah.
Mmm.
Let me get down there and just give you
some of my attention.
Mmm.
Bring your sweet little pussy right over
here.
Yeah.
Oh.
I want you to pack your little butt over
there.
I'll go see if my mom's home.
Oh, okay.
Hey, Paul, look.
God, you're always so horny on that.
Paul, I didn't know you were home.
Hello, Sherry.
Hello, Mrs. Scar.
Honey, I'm sorry I
didn't fix supper tonight,
but your decrepit
old mother has a date.
Melkin?
Well, I guess you won't be getting home so
pretty late, huh?
Probably will be pretty late.
Now, you two don't work too hard.
Well, have a good time.
Thank you.
Oh.
Hey, what are you doing over there in the
corner, baby?
Well, what if I got bad breath and
something?
I'm just quite comfortable here,
thank you.
Oh, come on, a little closer.
I thought you were a swinger.
A swinger?
When I thought you were a pussycat.
What was it?
What did you say?
Nothing.
Nothing important.
That rotten cheater.
Oh, don't shoot with your hands.
Her body's moving and the sun beating
down.
Oh, I feel like I'm on fire.
Here she comes.
Oh, makes my skin bite shut.
Her body's ways to the sounds of the sea.
She's gotcha body in her eyes.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, she's got a dash.
Oh,
Gina tells me you just got a divorce.
You must be ready for some pretty heavy
action, huh, baby?
Is that what she told you?
Look, Charlie, maybe tonight wasn't such a
good idea.
I mean, where is this party, Monterey?
Hey, relax.
It's just a couple more miles down the
road.
Look, tick it easy, baby.
Just trust old Charlie.
Look where this rough face falls and I
love you.
Take a chance.
I'll feel her sauce, Charlie.
Our body's melting to the blaze of the
night.
Oh, I've never felt like this.
Oh, oh... She knows.
She knows.
Oh... I got my soul.
Yes, my partner.
Oh, I want to come.
Oh, yes, baby.
Oh, that's baby.
Oh, that comes.
Oh, yes.
Oh.
Oh, it looks 30 rounds.
Oh, it's got juicy shit.
Oh,
don't she get your hands?
Her body's moving and the sun's beating
down.
Oh, I feel like I'm on fire.
Here she comes.
Oh, I'll make my templature back.
Her body's way through the sounds of the
sea.
She's a devil in her eyes.
She's my man.
I'm a GP.
I've never talked to me like that before.
Yeah?
You know, you really turned me on,
honey.
Come on, baby.
Listen up.
No one's gonna bite you unless you want
them to.
What kind of a party is this?
The swing party.
Didn't Gina tell you anything?
No.
You mean swing like an orgy?
I think you'd better take me home.
Take you home.
Oh, shit.
I drove an hour and a half to get here.
And I'm not leaving.
Marlene, baby.
Am I glad to see you?
Come on, Charlie.
Feel like getting it on?
Come on, baby.
Don't be a party pooper.
I'm not budging from this spot.
Suit yourself, baby.
You can just sit here and wait for me.
My God, you're young enough to be my son.
Hey,
you're gorgeous looking, babe.
Please.
Let's see what you got into that dress.
No.
I just want to look a little, little bit.
What do you mean no?
I just want to take a look.
Stop.
Come on.
क्या तुम मेरे साथ थोड़ा दोस्ताना बर्ताव नहीं कर सकते?
“बस, बंद करो ये।
Let's go in the other room and get it on.
No.
Give yourself tight for it.
Oh, you got some nice melons there,
baby.
Please, please.
Stop that.
No.
Please.
Come on, let me take a look.
Come on.
No.
Stop.
Well, shit.
You're too tough for me, baby.
Oh, let me shoot.
Oh, God.
Come on.
The way down.
Oh.
Wow.
You really blew it.
Great crowd tonight, baby.
Great.
Yeah, really.
Christ, I'm drained.
Well, I'm ready.
Let's go, baby.
I came four times, you know.
तो फिर मैं तुम्हें अगले शुक्रवार कॉल करूँगा, जान।
अपना समय मत बर्बाद करो, चार्ली।
Jesus Christ.
Oh, my God.
प्रिय पॉल, कल रात हम अपना आपा खो बैठे।
जो हमने किया वह बहुत ही गलत था।
जब मैं आज रात घर आऊँगी, तब हम इस पर बात करेंगे।
अपनी माँ से प्यार करो।
बारबरा, क्या तुम कृपया फोन उठाओगी?
ओह, तुम हो, जीना।
मैं अभी बात नहीं कर सकती।
मैं बहुत परेशान हूँ।
मैं तुम्हें बाद में फोन करूँगी।
चार्ली ने बहुत बेहूदा व्यवहार किया, और पार्टी बहुत ख़राब थी।
हमारी पूरी ज़िंदगी बिखर रही है।
मैं तुमसे बाद में बात करूँगी।
क्या बात है, जान?
क्या परेशानी है?
इतना भी बुरा नहीं हो सकता।
तुम आज छुट्टी क्यों नहीं ले लेती?
लेकिन मेरे पास बहुत सारा काम है।
ये क्या बेहूदा बात है?
मैं तुम्हें बताता हूँ कि मैं क्या करूँगा।
मैं भी आज छुट्टी ले लूँगा।
हम दोपहर के खाने के लिए समुद्र तट पर जाएँगे।
शायद हम थोड़ी देर बाद तट वाली सड़क पर ड्राइव पर निकल जाएँ।
अरे चलो, आखिर मैं ही तो मालिक हूँ।
No.
Call zero here.
I ain't see three days.
Right up this way for the hot news.
ताज़ा खबरों के लिए इस तरफ़ चलिए।
I ain't see three days.
Easy to make me up to me.
Oh,
it's easy to come and come.
I can't have a
garden as a lake back.
And it'll show you love to me.
It's plenty of time.
Oh, please, please, please.
We've got all night long, and it's easy.
Making sweet love on the roof.
Thanks for today, Jerry.
It really helped a lot.
You know me, good guy, Morgan.
Let's go in.
It's been years since I've seen Paul.
I'd like to see him again.
No, Jerry, not tonight.
Listen, you're a very sweet guy,
and I had a wonderful time today.
But I tell you what, come over for supper
tomorrow night, okay?
Right now, I've got to go.
Oh, well.
Good guy will always get laid last.
हाँ, माँ, मैं यहीं हूँ।
नमस्ते, माँ।
अपने प्रेमी को इतना इंतज़ार क्यों करा रही हो??
पॉल, बात सच में गंभीर है।
कल रात जो हुआ, वह पूरी तरह मेरी गलती थी।
मैं नहीं चाहती कि तुम मेरे किए हुए काम के लिए खुद को दोषी समझो।
हम दोनों ने मिलकर किया था।
फिर से अपने लाड़ले बेटे को बाँहों में भरना वाकई बहुत अच्छा लगा।
बिल्कुल वैसे ही, जैसे जब तुम छोटे थे।
लेकिन यह बहुत गलत था।
देखो माँ, मैं हम दोनों के बारे में ज़रा भी बुरा नहीं सोचता।
जो हुआ, बस हो गया।
और सच कहूँ, मैं चाहता हूँ कि यह फिर से हो।
मत करो… मत करो।
नहीं, पॉल, मत करो।
इस बात के लिए दीवार पर भी गाली लिखी होती।
किसी को भी पता नहीं चलेगा
बस तुम और मैं—और कोई नहीं।
Paul, I'm talking about incest.
पॉल, मैं परिवार में यौन संबंध की बात कर रही हूँ।
Oh, my God.
Oh, shit.
वो कौन हो सकता है?
Oh.
Oh, my son.
ओह, मेरे बेटे
Oh.
Farla.
Barbara!
Am I in tribute to food?
ऐसा नहीं है।
I've just got my beautifully young stud in
there.
A little girl with the sweetest taste of pussy.
एक छोटी लड़की जिसकी चूत का स्वाद सबसे मीठा है।
Ever ate. कभी खाया।
But it's okay. लेकिन ठीक है।
So I'll miss a few more guys. इसलिए मुझे कुछ और लोगों की कमी खलेगी।
But what's the matter? लेकिन बात क्या है?
तुम अब भी चार्ली के साथ अपनी डेट को लेकर परेशान तो नहीं होना?
No.
बस मुझे किसी से बात करनी है।
And you're always so sure of yourself.
और तुम हमेशा खुद पर बहुत यकीन रखती हो।
Oh, I always say.
ओह, मैं हमेशा कहती हूँ।
जो स्वाभाविक लगे वही करो।
लेकिन तुम किस बारे में बात कर रही हो?
It's just that I can't say no to him.
बात बस इतनी सी है कि मैं उसे मना नहीं कर सकती।
I find myself wanting it to happen.
मुझे ऐसा लगता है कि मैं चाहती हूँ कि ऐसा हो जाए।
किसे मना करना है?
क्या करना चाहती हो
Paul.
पॉल और मैं.
We... Paul?
Paul?
क्या तुम मुझे ये बता रही हो कि तुमने... अपने बेटे पॉल से चुदवाया है?
सबसे बुरी बात तो ये है कि मुझे लगता है कि मैं
जेरी के प्यार में पड़ रही हूँ।
अरे, जेरी को भूल जाओ।
तुम अभी ब्रेकअप से ठीक रही हो
लेकिन मुझे पॉल के बारे में बताओ।
जब वो मुझे छूता है, जब... when every hand's
touched my body, I just
want him inside of me.
Did he eat you?
Did you let him eat your pussy?
Let him.
He just did it.
ओह भगवान, यह तो बहुत रोमांचक है।
क्या तुमने उसका लंड चूसा?
क्या वह तुम्हारे मुँह मे ही झड़ गया?
Lots of it.
Gobbs and gobs have come.
Oh, God.
ओह, मैं झड़ रही हूँ।
Oh,
मुझे इस पर यक़ीन नहीं हो रहा है।
Gina, I come to you for help and you're
having orgasms all over the room.
अब मैं क्या करूँ!
इसका विरोध मत करो।
यह कैसी सलाह है?
I'm from my best friend too.
मुझे माफ़ करना, बारबरा।
मुझे समझ नहीं आ रहा कि क्या कहूँ।
मैंने कभी किसी को नहीं देखा जो अपने बेटे से चुदवाया हो।
वाह, तुमसे तो बड़ी मदद की
तुम ठीक रहोगे ना…
Where are you going?
I don't know where I'm going.
I'll talk to you later.
Oh, I'm so horny.
Oh, God.
Imagine fucking her own son.
Hey, sweetheart.
When do we eat?
In a few minutes.
No, no, Paul might see us.
Listen to you two.
Be sure and keep next weekend open.
We're going to do a little traveling.
Traveling?
Yes, didn't I tell you?
I don't want a little cabin at Lake Tahoe.
No, Jerry, you didn't.
It must be lovely this time of year.
We'll go up.
We'll get a little son.
We'll do a little gangly.
How does that sound?
It sounds lovely.
I can't make it.
I'm going to be busy.
I'll see you later.
What's the matter?
You've hardly eaten anything.
It seemed to have lost my appetite.
Maybe had a date.
Oh, you know how teenagers are.
Oh, we're alone at last.
All this eating is making me hungry.
Come up here and give me dessert.
You may not know this barber, but I've
always been in love with you.
I think I sort of did know, Jerry.
Easy to make love to you.
You better plan it on because you re-put
your soul.
You can't have a garden that the flowers
don't grow.
It's easy to close.
You better plan it on because you re-put
your soul.
You can't have a garden that the flowers
don't grow.
It's easy to move in close to you.
Oh, we found a touch.
Don't let this feel in close.
Not asking much, please.
Don't tease me.
Let yourself go because it's easy.
Easy to make love to you.
I hope you feel the same way about me that
I feel about you.
You know I want to marry you, honey.
Jerry, you may be very happy, but please
don't rush me.
I just have to rearrange my priorities.
What do you mean you rearrange your
priorities?
It's just that from now on, my life is my
life.
And I'm going to do things my way.
And part of my way is keeping you as my
lover.
And the other part of your way?
Mmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm
hmm hmm
hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm
hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm h